[SPEAKER_00]: Twelve different product groups at the company and all of the people who are running them With the exception of one Did not join the company running a product group or reporting to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's amazing And the one exception was is David Marcus who was the CEO of a
[SPEAKER_00]: you know, a fifty billion dollar public company.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, I'm pretty happy that he's on board and having him run a product group I think is a pretty big coup too.
[SPEAKER_00]: But literally none of them started off reporting to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, they all started off in different roles, some were engineers, some were data analysts, some were product managers, and they've all grown.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I think what happens is, you know, people see that you create opportunities for people and that also, I think, keeps the best people engaged and makes the best people want to come work at your company because they feel like, oh, I'm going to get those kind of opportunities too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you most excited about over the next twenty years?
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you think will be the major transformations?
[SPEAKER_01]: How will Facebook transform?
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you think the rest of the world will transform?
[SPEAKER_00]: So we have this ten year roadmap.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, three of the big changes that we want to see in the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we're focused on three things.
[SPEAKER_00]: Connectivity, it's getting everyone in the world on the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right now more than half the world is not on the internet, which is
[SPEAKER_00]: I think a lot of people in Silicon Valley probably take this for granted, the internet, because it just is not uniformly available.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if we want to solve a lot of the big challenges of the world today, there are not problems that any one group of people or even one country can solve.
[SPEAKER_00]: They really involve coming together and giving everyone an opportunity to participate in solving them.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think connecting everyone is really a key thing, which is going to be great for people around the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: The next one is AI.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that that's just going to unlock so much potential in so many different domains.
[SPEAKER_00]: We use it at Facebook for a lot of different things, for showing people content that they're going to find more meaningful, for making sure that you connect with the people you actually care about on the service.
[SPEAKER_00]: But in a lot of ways, the work that we're doing on AI to push the fundamental state of